digplanet.com 2016-06-28

# Digparty > Privacy Policy

Digparty's Privacy Policy

Digparty's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using Digparty, located at www.digparty.com and its directly associated domains (collectively, "Digparty" or "Website")

By using or accessing Digparty, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## The Information We Collect

When you visit Digparty you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

When you enter Digparty, we may collect your browser type and IP address. This information is may be gathered for all Digparty visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in.

You schedule and attend Digparty sessions (as defined in the Digparty Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Digparty may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of the Digparty service through the operation of the service (e.g., photo tags) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.

By using Digparty, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

## Use of Information Obtained by Digparty

Profile information is used by Digparty primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information.

Digparty may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. 

Digparty may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people like a band or movie and personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide you Digparty. We believe this benefits you. You can know more about the world around you and, where there are advertisements, they're more likely to be interesting to you.

We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to newspapers and Internet sources such as blogs, instant messaging services, Digparty Platform developers and other users of Digparty, to supplement your profile. 

## Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

Digparty is about sharing information with others — friends and people who host and attend a Digparty session.

We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about Digparty, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Digparty-specified purposes.

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Digparty service or using the Digparty name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

We may offer stores or provide services jointly with other companies on Digparty. We may share customer information with that company in connection with your use of that store or service.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Digparty business, or individual business units owned by Digparty were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

## Links

Digparty may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Digparty.

## Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on Digparty are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Digparty does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Digparty unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Digparty and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

## Security

Digparty takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or your password), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). (To learn more about SSL, go to <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer>

## Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of Digparty, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
